谁?
Who is it?
Tom
It's Tom.
Tom 你丈夫?
Tom,your husband?
他来干什么?
What's he doing here?
什么事?
Uh,what's going on?
抱歉 我知道我不该来
I'm sorry,I know I'm not supposed to be here,
但明天得交Evelyn的入学同意书
but Evelyn's school contract's due tomorrow.
我就知道忘了什么
I knew I was forgetting something.
我去找支笔
Let me,uh,find a pen.
不知Emily Post对这种场面 会作何建议 (礼仪学家)
Not quite sure what Emily post recommends in this situation,
我是Tom
but I'm Tom.
Damien 你好
Damien. Hey.
抱歉打扰了 我--
Sorry to intrude. I just--
不知她什么时候会回来
I wasn't quite sure when she'd be coming home.
不要紧
No problem.
谢谢你特地送来
Thank you so much for catching this.
没事
Yeah.
我这就走
Well,I'll get out of your way,
很高兴见到你 晚点见 宝贝
it was good to meet you,and I'll see you later,hon.
再见
Bye.
那么...
So...
他看来人不错
Seems like a nice guy.
Jules 你还好吗?
Jules,you okay?
不 我的肚子
No,my stomach.
过来 躺下
Here. Lie down.
- 试着... - 把Tom叫住
- Try to-- - get Tom.
Tom!
知道啥叫完美吗?
You know what would be perfect?
法式土司塔
French toast tower.
你还在Mickey餐馆吃饭?
You still go to Mickey's?
你胆固醇飙多高了?
What's your cholesterol?
我就这点小毛病 我留着好了
It's my one vice. I'm keeping it.
那我也舍命陪君子吧
As much as I would love to clog my arteries,
但我十点要做CT 还得赶回家换衣服
I have a 10:00 ct and I still have to race home,get changed.
你大可留几件衣服在这
Maybe you could keep some clothes here.
也许吧
Maybe I could.
他想偷穿你裙子
He's just trying to get into your skirts.
这可不是比喻
And I don't mean metaphorically.
反正他有双美腿
Well,he's got the legs for it.
那今晚再见?
So I will see you tonight?
好咧
Yeah.
再见 House
Bye,House.
过得开心
Have a nice day.
"过得开心"? 真有礼貌
"Have a nice day. " How civilized.
我说了不会妨碍你俩
I said I'd stay t of it.
- 怎么了? - 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
- 肯定有什么 - 没
- Clearly something. - Nope.
House 以你的性格
House,on a list of your attributes,
从来不会吞吞吐吐
there's nothing that even rhymes with "coy.
好吧 我在冰箱里有发现
" Okay,I may have seen something in the fridge.
比如说 你们关系的终结
Like the end of your relationship.
她把牛奶放冰箱门而不是架子上
She put the milk in the door and not on the shelf.
这没啥大不了
It's not a big deal.
你不喜欢这样 但你没出声
You hate that she did that,but you didn't say anything.
你这是挑拨离间
You're trying to get us to fight.
不 我这是帮你忙
No,I'm trying to help.
你有意见该直说
If you got an issue,let her know.
我就知道 你没那么容易收手
I should have known that you weren't done sabotaging this.
行 你继续屈憋着
Fine. Stew in your irritation.
上次也是这种小事 堆积成怨恨和愤怒
And sure,last time it bubbled over into resentment and rage,
最终以一纸离婚书收场
leading ultimately to a painful divorce
你俩至今都没能走出阴霾
that neither of you ever really recovered from,
这下又有好戏看了
but I'm sure this time it'll be great.
这病例好玩 35岁女性 发烧并伴有腹部疼痛
Interesting case. 35-year-old woman with fever and abdominal pain.
急诊排除了所有常规性的可能
E. R. ruled out all the usual suspects.
别说了 我快被你逗死了
Stop before you interest me to death.
她实行开放婚姻
And she's in an open marriage.
这不是好玩 是怪异
That's not interesting. It's just weird.
知道什么比这更怪吗? 人类一开始就遵循一夫一妻制
Know what's weirder? That other humans are monogamous in the first place.
其它物种都不止一个配偶 如果你想搬出天鹅反驳我
No other species on the planet mates for life and if you're gonna bring up swans,
它们和其它动物一样偷腥
they cheat like everybody else.
不过它们比兔子会搞公关
They just have better pr than rabbits.
动物还吃自己的幼崽 杀死对手
Animals also eat their young and kill their rivals.
多数人不这么干 这也怪?
That make it weird that most of us don't?
这话竟出自一个 四处拈花惹草的家伙之口?
Says the guy whose opposable thumbs have been all over
除了家花 你还藏着几朵野花?
how many women who aren't his wife?
行得通的开放婚姻跟独角兽一样
A functional open marriage is like a Unicorn.
是不存在的虚构生物
It's a mythical creature that doesn't exist.
到头来总会有人不开心
Someone always ends up unhappy.
这会儿不开心的是病人 她正备受肠道阻塞的煎熬
Our patient's unhappy because she's suffering from an intestinal blockage.
无聊的诊断
Boring.
还得找个理由排除它
Then we have to find a reason to rule it out.
疱疹性结肠炎?
What about herpes colitis?
从某个性伴侣身上传染的疱疹
She picks up the infection from one of her partners.
- 在结肠安家落户 - 性病检查呈阴性
- It takes root in her colon. - Std panel was clean.
照我看 这对夫妻一开始就不开心
Chances are,this couple was unhappy in the first place.
他们想挽救从不存在的...
This is their attempt to save something that never--
继续
go on.
疱疹若是六周内感染的 可能查不出
Herpes might not register if she was exposed in the last six weeks.
但用钡灌肠能查出
But it would show up on a barium enema.
等等 你亲自做检查?
Wait. You're gonna do it?
我得看看病人是独角兽 还是匹水性杨花的母马
Gotta see if our patient's a Unicorn or just a slutty horse.
探究Taub何以乐于此道
Think how much fun Taub could be having.
钡会覆盖结肠内壁
Barium coats the inner lining of your colon.
能拍出清晰的X光片
Lets us get a good look at it on the X-ray.
我可以找人去接Evelyn
I can get somebody else to pick up Evelyn.
我这会儿不能抛下你
I feel like i'm abandoning you.
我吃止痛片了
I'm on painkillers.
我可不希望你以后看我屁股时 总想起这画面
I'd rather this not be what you think of every time you look at my butt.
好了 翻个身
Okay,roll onto your side.
开始加料了
It's fill 'er up time.
Evelyn是他新对象?
So is Evelyn his new squeeze?
是我们的女儿
She's our daughter.
从小看加尔各答风情画 长大 一定很有趣 (讲述性的百老汇剧)
Must be interesting growing up in a production of Oh! Calcutta!
她才六岁
She's six.
她对性的认识 不比同龄人多
She knows as much about our sex life as any other kid her age.
你大可向她解释 你们因为她才没离婚
You can explain that she's the reason the two of you stayed married.
你才呆五分钟 便以为看透了我们
You've been in the room five minutes. You got us all figured out.
但你忽略了我们相爱的事实
Of course,you left out the part where we love each other
我们想白头偕老
and we want to grow old together.
但不想青春作伴
But you just don't want to be young together.
你想 无数夫妻和我们做着同样的事
Look,when you think about it,tons of couples do what we do.
区别在于 多数情况下 其中一方被蒙在鼓里
It's just that with most of them,one spouse doesn't know about it.
我们只是坦诚相告罢了
We decided things work better when people tell each other the truth.
灌满了
Tank's full.
我去找放射科的小精灵
I'll page the radiology elves.
我没说我讨厌这领带
I'm not saying I hate it.
只是和你眼睛颜色不搭
Just doesn't go with your eyes.
- 你讨厌它 - 有点
- You hate it. - Little bit.
还要对我外表进行残酷批判吗?
Any more heartless critiques of my general appearance?
不 说完了
Nope. All done.
她真如看上去那么骚?
So is she as bendy as she looks?
我和Maya是普通朋友而已
Maya and I are just friends.
不 我和你才是普通朋友 没见你每周跟我喝三次咖啡
No,you and I are friends and you don't have coffee with me three times a week.
她很有趣
She's an interesting person.
在俄亥俄州长大 有三个兄弟
She grew up in Ohio. She has three brothers.
还真有趣啊 但上周那个 柬埔寨化验员告诉我们
Fascinating. Last week,that Cambodian lab tech was telling us
他如何在战场挣扎求存时 你打着呵欠去吃甜甜圈了
how he survived the Killing Fields and you left to go get a donut.
我们就调笑下 图个好玩
So we flirt. It's fun.
这很危险 那女人绝对会上你
It's dangerous. That woman would totally do you.
真的?
You think?
什么事也不会发生
Nothing is gonna happen.
我意思是如果你想减肥
All I'm saying is if you want to be on a diet,
就别在甜点车旁晃悠了
you might want to stop hanging out by the dessert cart.
X光没查出问题 不是疱疹性结肠炎 她肚子也不痛了
X-ray was clean. She doesn't have herpes colitis or abdominal pain.
做X光时就不痛了
It stopped hurting during the X-ray,
就是说本来是肠道阻塞 现在通了 她可以出院了
which means it was just an intestinal blockage that passed. We should discharge her.
当然了
Absolutely.
没必要找出潜在病因
There's no need to find any underlying cause
反正这事不可能再发生
'cause these things never happen twice.
查下她的消化系统
Take her digestive system for a test drive.
给她喝杯X线阻射奶昔
Give her a radio-opaque milkshake.
隔15分钟做一次X光
X-ray every 15 minutes to see
看是否有异常阻断
if it makes any unscheduled stops on the way through.
那我们得呆上一整晚
We'll be here all night.
不 是Taub要呆上一整晚
No,Taub will be here all night.
和独角兽谈谈 完了告诉我 你还不相信开放婚姻
Talk to the Unicorn and then tell me you don't believe.
我今天给一个孩子做腹部CT
I did an abdominal ct on a kid today
发现有个六英寸的团块 全是口香糖
and found a six-inch bezoar made entirely of gum.
什么人啊 给三岁孩子吃这么多...
I mean,who gives a three-year-old an endless supply of g--
- 你怎么了? - 没事
- you okay? - Yeah.
里面还有头发 纸头什么的
I mean,there was hair in it and maybe a piece of paper.
你结婚多久了?
So... how long you been married?
这就是开放婚姻的缺点之一
One of the few drawbacks of having an open marriage.
没人会和我聊比赛或天气
Nobody ever asks me about current events or the weather.
洋基队这赛季表现不错
Yankees look good this season.
七年了
Seven years.
那什么时候开始--?
And,uh,how long have you-- you know?
婚后三年 我们发现 传统婚姻不适合我们
After three years,we realized that traditional marriage was making us both miserable.
多数人会选择离婚
Most people get divorced at that point.
我们不想离婚 我们仍深爱彼此
Yeah,we didn't want to get divorced. We still loved each other.
只是我们发现 指望一个人...
We just realized that
能满足你所有欲望 是不切实际的
expecting one person to fulfill all of your needs forever is unrealistic.
坚持一夫一妻的夫妇也能过得幸福
There are happy monogamous couples out there.
对啊 总有那么一两对模范夫妇
Sure. One or two have the perfect marriage.
于是其他人也学着降低了要求
Everybody else has figured out how to settle for less.
我不想将就过 到头来怨恨我丈夫
I don't want to settle and end up resenting my husband.
他做不到的10% 我可以从其人身上弥补
I'd rather g the 10% he doesn't give me somewhere else
这样我就能感激他所做的90%
so that i can really appreciate him for the 90% he does.
有点不对劲
I think something's wrong.
- 是肚子吗? - 我心跳加快了
- With your stomach? - My heart is racing.
深呼吸
Try and take deep breaths.
我试着给你心跳减速
I'm going to try to slow your heart down.
是因为肠道阻塞?
Is this because of the blockage?
不好 没用
No. It's not working.
叫辆急救车来!
Need a crash cart in here!
我需要你半年内所有性伴侣的名单
I need a list of all your sexual partners from the last six months.
为什么?
Why?
你妻子的心律不齐
Your wife had an arrhythmia.
症状从肠道转移到了心脏
The progression of symptoms from bowel to heart
极有可能是感染了寄生虫
makes a parasitic infection most likely.
既然Julia没出过国...
Since Julia hasn't been out of the country--
我最近只去过内布拉斯加州出差
the only place that I've been recently is a business trip to Nebraska.
但你们可能从性伴侣身上传染了
But either of you could have picked up a bug from one of your partners.
情况有点...复杂
It's kind of... complicated.
你到底有几个床伴? 说个大概
How many partners are we talking about? Ballpark.
- 没有 - 没有?
- None. - None?
我们的性生活很和谐
We have a great sex life.
我不需要其他人
I don't need anyone else.
那为什么不告诉她 结束这场闹剧?
So why not just tell her that and close this whole thing up?
- 你结婚了吗? - 我...结过
- You married? - I-- I was.
那你有没试过陪老婆看言情片
Did you ever agree to go see a chick flick with your wife
或假装享受古典乐?
or pretend to enjoy classical music?
史特拉芬斯基又不会和我老婆 在市郊旅馆开房 (俄罗斯作曲家)
Stravinsky never groped my wife in a Midtown hotel room.
她需要这个
She needs this.
我不需要
I don't.
但我不想让她负疚
But I don't want her to feel bad about that.
他说谎
He's lying.
他有权出轨 何必隐瞒?
Guy's got a license to drill. Why would he lie about not using it?
我不是指这个
That's not the lie.
是他谎称为顾全妻子感受
The lie is that he gives a crap about how his wife feels.
如果双方都鬼混 这另当别论
If they're both screwing around,that's one thing.
既然女方有而男方没有
But if she has a piece on the side and he doesn't,
他肯接受的唯一可能就是
the only way he'd be okay with that is
他在其它方面背叛了她
if he's betraying her in some other way that,
这样他才能找到心理平衡
in his mind,makes them even.
我们的独角兽不是独角兽
My Unicorn isn't a Unicorn.
而是头顶马桶搋子的驴子
It's a donkey with a plunger stuck to its face.
没错 即便这家伙不出轨 也得找个见不得人的理由
Right. Even the guy who's not cheating is doing it for underhanded reasons.
不 不 他这不是挑刺
No,no,no. He's not being cynical.
他认为丈夫背地里在干什么 所以双方扯平了
He's assuming the husband is doing something to even the score,
就是说 他认为夫妻之道有公平可言
which means he thinks there is a score,
也就是说 天鹅偷腥只是幌子 House其实是一夫一妻拥护者
which means,cheating swans aside,House believes in monogamy.
看他多浪漫啊
He's being romantic.
我拥护的是"人性妒忌"论
What I believe is that men are genetically engineered to be jealous.
问题不是我怎么认为 而是他认为
Doesn't matter if i think there's a score. I guarantee you he does.
妻子的床伴有可疑吗?
Any of the wife's partners pan out?
过去半年内 除了Tom 她还和另外两人一起
She's been with two people other than Tom in the last six months.
他们都没离开过三州交界区 (指纽约 新泽西和康提涅格)
Neither of them have been outside the tri-state area.
那就是丈夫的问题了
So we're back to the husband.
- 你刚才还说... - 背着老婆搞小动作
- You just said you believed-- - he's doing something behind her back.
有什么比去内布拉斯加 出差更好的借口?
What better cover than a business trip to Nebraska?
说的真有这地方似的
Like that's really a place.
找出他出差的证明 然后回去开工
Let's find his travel records and get back to work.
看来你能接受这对夫妻的做法
You seem pretty mellow about this couple's deal.
我还以为你会第一个反对
Thought you'd be first in line to shake a finger.
至少他们能维持婚姻 但我不能
They're still married. I'm not.
反正我办不到这样
Not that I could ever do it.
我嫉妒House 尽管Cameron碰都没碰过他
I was jealous of House and Cameron never touched him.
你没算上精神出轨
Not counting the emotional fondling.
我妈临死前 我爸有了外遇
When my mom was dying,my dad had an affair.
他告诉你的?
He told you this?
我看到他们一起下车
I'd seen them get out of his car.
我妈去世后两年 他们结婚了
Two years after mom died,they got married.
你一定很难过吧
That must have sucked.
当时是的
At the time,yeah.
但回想起来...没什么不好的
But looking back... It makes sense.
我妈始终蒙在鼓里 他也可以有个人排遣孤寂
My mom never knew about it and he needed someone to make him feel less alone.
他不眠不休照顾了我妈两年半 直到她去世
He took care of my mom day in and day out for 2 1/2 years before she died.
他对她很好
He was devoted to her.
爱上别人不会改变这点
Loving someone else didn't change that.
那么说 如果其中一方快死了 另一方就可以同时爱两个人?
So loving two people at once is fine as long as one of them is dying?
不管谁在我生病时照顾我
Whoever's taking care of me when I get sick,
我也希望有人能照顾他
I hope they've got someone else to take care of them.
Tom说的是实话
Tom was telling the truth.
他真去了内布拉斯加
He really did go to Nebraska.
有机票和餐厅收据为证
Plane ticket and restaurant seats.
别纠结内布拉斯加了
Forget Nebraska.
寄生虫可能是商场买来的
Maybe they just bought their parasites at the mall.
咱该把家里丝瓜络扔了
You know,we should really throw away that loofah.
那些都是舶来品 可能未经消毒
They're imported. Sometimes they're not sterilized.
病人可能因为用它得了变形虫病
We think our patient got amoebiasis from hers.
她不会有事吧?
Is she gonna be okay?
我们正在治疗 应该没事的
We're treating now. She should be fine.
这病人有点特殊
It's actually kind of bizarre.
他们夫妇实行开放婚姻
She and her husband have an open marriage.
他们和别人睡?
They sleep with other people?
她是这么做的 她丈夫也没意见
Well,she does. Her husband's totally fine with it.
这太出格了 是吧?
I mean,it's crazy,right?
你提这事是想...?
And you're bringing this up because?
觉得有意思罢了
I thought it was interesting.
比别的病例更有意思么
More interesting than your other cases,I guess.
你通常会聊同事 损House
I mean,you talk about your colleagues,you rant about House.
但很少提病人
You don't usually mention your patients.
你也想要开放婚姻?
Is open marriage something you want?
不
No.
我是说...
I mean...
我知道你不会...
I know you'd never...
长久以来 你大费周章地 向我证明你没外遇
All this time and energy you spent convincing me you weren't cheating...
你的确有别的人
And there's somebody else.
- 我没-- - 加水吗 先生?
- I'm not-- - some more water sir?
好吧
Okay.
医院里有个女的
There's a woman at work.
人人都说她对我有意思 但我什么都没做过
People say she's attracted to me,but nothing's happened.
也不会去做 我没出轨
Nothing's going to happen. I'm not having an affair.
但你想出轨
But you want to.
不 亲爱的
No,honey.
我在向你坦白
I'm trying to be honest.
并非想重蹈覆辙
I don't want to make the same mistakes.
那你老实说
Be honest then.
你对她有想法吗?
Are you attracted to her?
听我说...
Look...
她很有魅力
she's attractive.
我承认被她吸引
There's an attraction.
你对其他男人就没这感觉吗?
Aren't there men who make you feel that way?
当然有 但我从未想过付诸行动 因为--
Of course there are,but it never occurs to me to act on it because--
因为我是有夫之妇 我有了你
because I'm married... To you.
我就知足了
And that's enough for me.
我不能满足你吗?
Aren't I enough for you?
你当然可以
Of course you are.
病人的腿动不了了
Our patient's lost all movement in her legs.
有其他医生在呢 Chris 我们还没聊完
There are other doctors,Chris. We're talking.
对不起
I'm sorry.
病人瘫痪了
The woman's paralyzed.
我打车走
I'll get a cab.
化验结果显示 无脊髓受损迹象 无大脑损伤和出血
Tests show no spinal cord injury,no cerebral lesions,no hemorrhage.
粪便样本测试显示 不是丝瓜络搞的鬼
Finally got a stool sample. The loofah's innocent.
没发现阿米巴虫和其它寄生虫
No sign of amoebas or any other parasites.
目前症状包括瘫痪 心率失常和间歇性腹痛
So paralysis,arrhythmia,and intermittent abdominal pain.
而且 他刮胡子时割破脸了
And he nicked himself shaving.
抱歉 我是说Taub
Sorry. That was Taub.
但这症状好解释
But it was easier to solve.
他用了储物柜里的破剃须刀 就是说他昨晚睡这了
Means he used the crappy razor in his locker,which means he slept here.
还不是你害的
Thanks to you.
我跟Rachel提开放婚姻的事
I brought up open marriage with Rachel.
结果异常惨烈
It was a disaster.
说正经的 我们排除了 性和外地感染的可能
On the medical front,we've knocked out sex and foreign travel.
也许是电解质失衡
Could be an electrolyte imbalance.
我被你的馊主意害惨了 你却史无前例地不追根问底?
So the only time you're not interested in my marriage is after you bw it up?
拿AV女优当婚姻顾问 你蠢到一定境界了
You're the moron who took marital advice from Tila Tequila.
你逼我这么做的
You pushed me into this.
我估摸这要么会拆散你俩 要么逼你们坦诚相对
Figured it would either blow up your marriage or make it more honest.
- 都对你有好处 - 性方面呢?
Either way,you win. What about sex?
回到病人 你们没意见吧?
I'm talking about the patient. Is that cool with everybody?
性因素已经排除了
We've ruled out sex.
我们排除了与她发生关系的人
We ruled out sex with other people.
Tom说每周和Julia亲热三到四次
Tom said he and Julia have been doing it three or four times a week
她在外面还有人
and she's got boys on the side.
性欲过盛是肾上腺皮质癌的症状
Increased libido can be a symptom of adrenocortical carcinoma,
可以解释她其它症状
which also explains her other symptoms.
女人喜欢做爱就有病?
A woman who likes sex must be sick?
虽说在座各位同仁都希望
Just because everybody in this room wishes
女人时刻饥渴着 奈何天不遂人愿
that all women were horny all the time doesn't make it so.
给她做肾上腺核磁共振
Get an mri of her adrenal glands.
体育版给我好吗?
Okay if I take the sports page?
行
Sure.
用下杯垫行吗?
Would you mind using a coaster?
噢 当然 抱歉
Oh. Sure. Sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我还希望厕纸用完时 你能主动换一卷
Also,it'd be great if you'd replace the toilet paper when you finish a roll.
往洗碗机里堆碗碟时
And when you load the dishwasher,
大且平的碗不能放在底层
you can't put a big,flat bowl on the bottom.
否则水都在碗里转 其他碗碟洗不到
It traps the water so nothing on the top gets clean.
还有拜托别把香蕉皮扔卧室垃圾桶
And please don't throw banana peels in the bedroom trash.
这都不是我干的
I haven't done any of those things.
你可能不自觉--
You're probably not even aware of--
我讨厌香蕉
I hate bananas.
天呐 是House干的
Oh,my God. It was House.
对不起 他一直在挑拨我们
I'm sorry. He's been trying to get us to fight.
他为什么做这些来挑拨?
Why would he think that stuff would make us fight?
因为牛奶
Because of the milk.
你把牛奶放冰箱门上了
You put it in the door.
冰箱的主体是最凉的部分
The body of the refrigerator is the coldest part.
但门的温度不稳定 食品质量没法保证
The temperature in the door fluctuates,which decreases shelf life.
你啥时开始有强迫症了?
When did you get all ocd?
我只是想碗碟干净 牛奶新鲜 保障咱的健康
I just want clean dishes and unspoiled milk so we can all stay healthy.
噢 原来是为健康着想
Oh,it's about health.
那杯垫呢? 用了会补充维生素B12?
What about the coaster? Does that replenish my B-12 or something?
- 不谈这个了行吗? - 没问题
- Can we just drop it? - Sure.
我们没离婚时 你就对这些耿耿于怀?
You have this list of annoyances the entire time we were married?
快点好起来 妈妈
Get better,mommy.
我爱你 小兔子
I love you,rabbit.
Julia 有人来看你
Julia,you have a guest.
现在不方便
This isn't a good time.
Hadley医生 娱乐室有电子游戏吗?
Dr. Hadley,did you say there was a video game in the playroom?
你教我打游戏吧
Maybe you can teach me how to play one of them.
放射科见
See you in radiology.
从我老婆病房滚出去
Get out of my wife's room.
你们的关系不能越界
Your relationship with her stays out of our space.
我很担心她
I was worried about her.
Tom说的对 你还是走吧
Tom's right. You should go.
我们上床可以 探病就不--
So it's fine if we have sex,but if I drop by to see if you're okay--
这是家庭场合
this is our family.
对不起
Sorry.
我做实习医生时 穿了两年缩水衬衫
I spent two years of residency wearing shirts that were a size too small.
告诉我一声别烘干有那么难吗?
How hard is it to ask me not to put them in the dryer?
我帮你洗衣服 因为你基本不在家
And I only did your laundry because you were never home.
- 我又没让你洗 - 你当然没有
- I didn't ask you to. - Of course you didn't.
但哪天没干净内裤穿了 你还不心烦气燥的
You just got annoyed whenever you didn't have clean underwear.
我没说我生气啊
I never said I was annoyed.
这就是问题了 你什么都不说
That's the point. You didn't say anything.
哟 你倒好意思怪我啥都不说
So I'm getting a lecture on communication from someone
当初说要离婚 你还是通过律师转达我的
who had her lawyer inform me our marriage was over.
开口提开放婚姻 你胆子忒大了
Asking for an open marriage. You got stones.
谈判变逼供 场面何惨烈
Conversation sort of got away from me. It was a train wreck.
我觉得你提出是好事
I think it's good you brought it up.
我读过一篇研究报告 说是具多重血管加压素受体的男性
I read a study that found men who have multiple copies of a certain vasopressin receptor
不忠几率比常人高一倍
are twice as likely to be unfaithful.
也许你也在此列
Maybe you're just one of those guys.
那么说 我出轨是天生的 好极了
So my cheating is biologically predetermined? Fantastic.
放大五倍 得看仔细她的骨髓
Multiply times five. We need a better look at the medulla.
还以为你会如释重负
I thought you'd be relieved.
这能洗脱你的罪名 都是基因的错
This gets you off the hook. It's just genetics.
我身高168 发际线不断后退
I'm 5'6" and have a receding hairline.
我恨基因 骨髓没问题
I hate genetics. Medulla's clean.
没见你穿增高鞋 也没植发
I don't see you wearing lifts or hair plugs.
因为我矮且秃并不伤害任何人
That's because being short and bald doesn't hurt anybody.
你死不承认的毛病也是基因作怪
The only thing hurtful about your other genetic predisposition
但这就会伤害人了
is that you keep denying it.
对你和Rachel都不好
It's not good for you or Rachel.
没发现异样 不是肾上腺癌
There's nothing there. It's not adrenal cancer.
也许你说的对
And maybe you're right about me.
但为了Rachel 我不会放弃的
But I'm not gonna stop trying. Rachel's worth it.
看那里
Look up there.
肺部 那是什么?
The lung. What is that?
我当时在新奥尔良开会
You served me with divorce papers
你就这么把离婚协议书甩来
in the middle of a medical conference in New Orleans.
我一激动 扔瓶子砸了面古董镜
I threw a bottle into an antique mirror.
你还会发泄情绪? 还真看不出来
Oh,you exhibited an emotion? I wish I'd known you were capable.
我当时多爱你啊 还想跟你去巴尔的摩 记得吗?
I loved you. I thought I was gonna be following you to Baltimore,remember?
我找了房子 还预约了工作面试
I called about apartments. I set up interviews.
我们的婚姻都名存实亡了 你还毫无知觉?
How could you think that we still had a real marriage?
我们好几月没好好说过话
We hadn't had a conversation in months.
因为我要打两份工养家
Maybe because I was working two jobs to support us.
不! 即使你在家 我也像对冰块讲话
No! No! It's because when you were home,it was like talking to a block of ice.
你明显在怨恨我
You were obviously so pissed off at me.
我起早贪黑还不是为 你能做那份无薪实习
I was killing myself so that you could take that non-paying internship.
是你支持我做的
That you said that I should take.
我想鼓励你! 我讨厌唱白脸!
I was trying to be supportive! Why do I have to be the bad guy?
有话直说不叫唱白脸
Expressing yourself does not make you the bad guy.
那好 那时的你是个自私的贱人
Okay,then. You were being a selfish bitch.
V/Q扫描证实 Julia肺部的黑点是血栓
VQ scan confirmed the spot on Julia's lung was a clot.
你说她丈夫会不会和充气娃娃做?
Think there's a chance the husband's a plushie?
我觉得血栓比这靠谱
If he has a secret,I highly doubt it's more relevant than the clot.
凝血障碍可以解释所有病症
Clotting disorder would explain everything.
问题是哪种障碍?
Question is,which one?
你从不看部门备忘录?
Do you read any of your departmental memos?
我只看标明"上班时间不宜浏览"的 (成人内容的讳称)
Only the ones labeled,"n-s-f-w.
会计部两天前就知会你 病人的保险事宜了
" Accounting notified you two days ago about your patient's insurance.
不好意思 不属于我浏览范围
Sorry,that's "n-n-s-f-w.
给你
" Here.
他没保险 别把他们整破产了
He doesn't have any. Try not to bankrupt them.
那些够他们破产的检查早做了
Oh,I'm long past the number of procedures that'll bankrupt them.
Julia有保险 入院表格上有保号
Julia's got insurance. I saw the policy number on the form.
但他们没交钱 保单失效了
But the policy lapsed due to non-payment.
我打了三通电话证实 你们早该发现的
I already made three calls about this. You should have been aware of that.
不可能 你们搞错了 我们有保险
No,there's just a mistake. Of course we have health insurance.
我们有阵子没交保费了
We're actually a little behind on the premiums.
但我会预支退休金来支付
But I pulled money out of my retirementccount to cover it.
他们说可以--
They said that we'll be fine in--
干嘛要预支退休金?
Why the retirement account?
我们先出去 你们单独聊--
We'll just give you a few minutes to--
把"们"去掉 她走我不走
and by "we," she means "she.
我把存款都用光了
" I lost all of our savings.
这听来像个秘密吧
Sounds like a secret to me.
我给她用了肝磷脂 阻止栓塞继续形成
I started her on heparin to prevent further clots,
但病因仍未知
but we still don't know what's going on.
我就知道这秘密和钱有关
Of course the husband's secret was money.
不是性 就是钱
If it's not sex,it's always money.
要么就是卖身换钱
Unless it's sex for money.
他到底怎么花光的?
How did he lose it anyway?
和病症无关 你不会感兴趣的
It's not medically relevant. You're not gonna care.
Wilson老教育我关心他人 说来听听
Wilson's been teaching me how to care. Try me.
他造风轮机出租给当地电力公司
He builds wind turbines and leases them out to local power companies.
你说的对 我不感冒
You're right. I don't care.
凝血障碍包括DIC 凝血因子突变 抗磷脂综合征
Clotting disorder: Dic. Factor five leiden,antiphospholipid syndrome.
维生素K缺乏症也符合
Vitamin k deficiency also fits.
造成血栓形成 且能解释腹痛
Causes thrombophilia and is consistent with abdominal pain.
恭喜你 House Sam把我踹了
Congratulations,House. Sam ended it.
怎么了?
What happened?
你验血去
Go test our patient's blood.
等五分钟也无妨
But it can wait five minutes.
把我们说的都测一遍
For everything we discussed.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
好歹你史无前例地承担责任了
Well,at least you're actually taking responsibility for once in your life.
很抱歉她甩了你 但不是我的错
Sorry that she left. It's not my fault.
我本想置身事外 是你逼我出手的
I didn't even want to get involved. You dragged it out of me.
那洗碗机怎解释 还有香蕉?
What about the dishwasher and the banana and the toi--
她才不是因为香蕉走人
she left because of the banana.
我只是想让你捍卫自己权益 说出你的要求
I just wanted you to stand up for yourself. Tell her what you want.
如果这使她再次离你而去
If doing that causes her to walk out for the second time,
你们的关系也长不了
well,your relationship wasn't gonna last anyway.
或者你可以别掺和
Or you could have stayed out of it.
我忍忍就过去了 虽偶尔有不爽
I could have kept my mouth shut,been annoyed sometimes,
但和她一起 我快乐得多
but I'd be happy,because I'd still be with her.
现在只能抱着冻牛奶过了
Now all I have is cold milk.
既然你恢复了自由身 一起吃个饭?
As long as you're free,you want to grab some dinner?
Tom晚上回家了?
Did Tom go home for the night?
我让他回去了 我不想让他陪
For starters. I told him to leave. I don't want him here.
钱的确是个复杂的问题
Money is a complicated subject.
不是因为钱
Yeah,it's not the money.
钱固然万恶 但...
I mean,the-- the money's bad,but...
我们刚开始开放婚姻时
When we first opened our marriage,
我和一个男人好上了 他骗我说是单身
I got involved with a guy who lied about being single.
有一天 他老婆打电话来
Then one day,his wife calls me.
大哭大喊 情绪彻底失控
She's crying and screaming and totally out of control.
我当时觉得很有...
And I felt...
优越感
superior.
以为自己不必经历这种痛苦
I thought I don't ever have to worry about feeling this way
因为我和Tom对彼此足够坦诚
because Tom and I are honest with each other.
看来我也不能免俗
Well,here I am.
对不起 昨晚我没回家
Sorry I didn't make it home last night.
有很多化验要做
I needed to run some tests.
你知道 得知你出轨后
You know what the worst part was?
什么最让我难过吗?
When y had your affair...
不是你和别人上床
Wasn't the sex.
而是那些谎言
It was the lies.
我意识到 我的生活都是假象
Realizing that the narrative of my life was totally wrong.
手术到很晚是假的
You weren't stuck in surgery.
出差也是假的
You weren't out of town.
我不想再次被耍了
I don't want to go through that again.
- 我说过什么事都不会-- - 仅周四晚
- I told you nothing's-- - Thursday nights.
午夜前必须回家
You have to be home by midnight.
不许带她回来
You don't bring her here.
不要告诉我她的事
You don't talk to her about me
我不想和她有任何交集
and I don't want to meet her ever in any context.
你这是同意我和其他女人上床?
Are you giving me permission to sleep with other women?
这不正合你意么?
It's what you want,isn't it?
我想要你
I want you.
你想要的不止我
You want more than me.
你要刺激
You want that thrill.
但我爱你
But I love you.
我相信你真心爱我...
And I really believe that you love me...
我们也算生活美满
And we have a good life together.
到这份上了 我要么走人
And at this point,either I walk away
要么接受真正的你
or I try to accept who you really are.
明天星期四
Tomorrow's Thursday.
没错
Yes,it is.
检测全部呈阴性
All our tests came back negative.
不是凝血障碍
It's not a clotting disorder.
那咱们还想别的法子
Which means we need to come up with a better idea.
什么能让胃 心脏 神经同时受损?
So what causes problems in the stomach,heart,nerves?
偶滴天呐
Oh,my God.
你想到了?
You know what it is?
Taub老婆对开放婚姻开绿灯了
Taub's wife gave the green light for an open marriage.
他喷了古龙水 但没散发羞愧的恶臭
He's wearing cologne,but not the stink of shame.
你有约了
You got a date.
我今晚要带着Rachel的祝福 去和Maya约会
I am going out with Maya tonight with Rachel's blessing.
该恭喜你?
Mazel Tov?
也许不是血液问题
Maybe the problem isn't her blood.
而是血管的问题
Maybe it's the vessels carrying the blood.
没有裂细胞或溶血症状
No sign of schistocytes or hemolysis.
你当真要睡了别人再回家陪老婆?
So you're actually going to sleep with another woman then go home to your wife?
谢天谢地 可算有人说回正题了
Thank God someone's keeping us focused on what's really important.
反正Taub本来也打算这么干
Taub was gonna do all of that anyway.
肺动脉高压
Pulmonary arterial hypertension.
成像显示肺动脉直径正常
Imaging showed normal diameter in her pulmonary artery.
我是这么想的--
Here's a thought--
Taub老婆现在算是自由身了
Taub's wife is now totally on the market.
介意给我她电话不?
Mind hitting me with her digits?
她肯定不介意 但办正事要紧
She would love that,but duty calls.
- 怎么了? - 我的肚子
- What's the matter? - My stomach.
- 和先前一个痛法? - 对 但更厉害了
- Same pain as before? - Yeah,but worse.
拿台便携超声波来 检查她的胃
Get the portable ultrasound in here. We need to get a look at her belly.
救我啊!
Help me!
胃痛走了没多会 转悠一圈又归来
Pain,pain went away,came back another day.
问题是怎么回来的?
Question is,what brought it back?
体表检查和超声都查不出
Physical exam was unrevealing. Ultrasound was clean.
完事后你在女友家还是回家洗澡?
So afterwards,are you gonna shower at your girlfriend's or at home?
病人 腹痛
Patient. Abdominal pain.
没错 我们六点前得结束这话题
Yeah,he's right. Let's get this wrapped up before 6:00.
Taub午夜就要变回忠诚大南瓜了
Taub turns back into a faithful Pumpkin at midnight.
病人入院之前 和男宠在一起
Patient was out with her boy toy before she came in.
也许胃痛是性兴奋激发的
Maybe the pain was triggered by sexual excitement.
一个人躺在病床上想 家里破产的事--真够嗨的
Because lying alone in a hospital bed contemplating bankruptcy-- hot.
我意思是 性兴奋是 副交感神经系统(PNS)的一项机能
My point was that arousal is a function of the parasympathetic nervous system.
如果这是问题所在 那哭也能引发疼痛--
If that's where the problem is, the pain could be triggered by crying,which seems--
PNS还控制消化功能
pns. Also controls digestion,
没看她喊破喉咙也能消化 说明问题不在这
which she's been doing without screaming her head off since she's been here.
但假如关键不在疼痛开始时 而是结束时呢?
What if what matters isn't when the pain started,but when it stopped?
那时她在做X光 你认为这能治好她?
It was during an X-ray. You think that cured her?
不是 但House给她做了钡灌肠造影
No,but House prepped her for the X-ray with a barium enema.
那东西什么用也不管 除了--
Well,that wouldn't treat anything except--
去吧
go.
部分肠管出现套叠 所以你会痛
You're in pain because part of your intestine folded in on itself.
这叫肠套叠
It's called an intussusception.
阻断血液流动 肠坏死前必须手术
It's cutting off blood flow. We need to fix it before your bowel gets necrotic and dies.
做完就没事了?
Once you do that,will I get better?
成年人得这病 一般是胃癌征兆
When this happens in adults,it's usually a sign of abdominal cancer.
套叠复位后 还得找肿瘤
We'll fix the overlap,and then search your intestine for tumors.
加奶泡吗?
Foam?
我有不详预感
I have a bad feeling about this.
老朋友不能给你买台意式咖啡机?
A friend can't spontaneously buy an overpriced italian espresso machine for another friend?
你又干什么了?
What did you do?
啥也没干 神奇吧
Nothing. That's the beauty.
我诚心诚意为Wilson好
I genuinely tried to help Wilson.
撺掇他捍卫自身权利 这建议很合情合理吧
I told him to stand up for himself,which you know is legitimate advice.
接着他俩就掰了
And his relationship blew up.
- 他没事吧? - 会好的
- Is he okay? - Ah,he'll be fine.
重点是 我顿悟了
Point is,I realized something.
因果循环 善有善报啊
I do nice things,nice things happen to me. Karma works.
你就到这发善心来了?
So you're paying it forward?
要这能把Lucas克死 或你给我口交也值了
If this should somehow lead to Lucas dying or oral sex,so be it.
阿弥陀佛
Namaste.
我今晚该打领带不?
Think I should wear a tie tonight?
你还真一点不含糊
This isn't weird at all.
今晚Rachel在哪儿吃饭?
I mean,where's Rachel eating tonight?
在家
Home.
要是她也有约呢?
What if she's going out too?
她有这权利 对吧?
She is allowed to,right?
当然 这才公平
Of course. It's only fair.
但我觉得她不会这么做
But I don't think she will.
你老婆只在家吃晚饭?
Your wife only eats dinner at home?
如果她约会别人
If she did go out,
虽然不好受
that would be tough,
但我能担待
but I think i can handle it.
你真能办到才夸这海口
Don't do it unless you're sure.
我宁当醋坛子也不想背着她来
I know I'd rather be jealous than a liar.
有发现
Got something here.
Kelly 钳子和手术刀
Kelly clamp and scalpel.
活检发现非特异性炎症
Biopsy showed non-specific inflammation,
指向炎症性肠病 但解释不了心脏问题
which suggests ibd,only it doesn't explain the cardiac problems.
还有肾功能衰退
Or her declining kidney function.
手术时做了测试
We ran panels during surgery.
炎症性肠病靠谱
Actually,ibd does make sense,
这会引发强直性脊椎炎
'cause it could trigger ankylosing spondylitis,
能解释心脏和肾的问题
which would explain the heart and the kidneys.
给她用柳氮磺吡啶和 肿瘤坏死因子抑制剂
Start her on sulfasalazine and tnf-inhibitors.
Taub 在你奔赴俄摩拉城前 我见不着你了 (圣经罪恶之都)
Oh,and Taub,I'm not gonna see you before you head off for gomorrah.
给你个建议 如果你昏头了...
Just remember,if you get disoriented...
深呼吸 寻找地平线的方向
Breathe through your nose and look for the horizon.
我办不到
I can't.
我本以为我可以
I really thought I could do this.
逻辑上天衣无缝
Logically,it makes perfect sense.
但是...
But...
整个下午
all afternoon,
我都在想
all I kept thinking about was
你俩一起时的情形
the two of you,together,
你爱抚她
and you touching her.
什么都没发生
Nothing's happened.
没事了
It's okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真的很想--
'Cause I really wanted it--
不
no.
我栽过一次了 除了你我谁也不要
I've been an idiot,and I don't need anything else. I just need you.
真心话?
You mean that?
是的
I do.
- 我爱你 Rachel - 我也爱你
- I love you,Rachel. - I love you too.
我们回家吧
Let's go home.
你能走了吗?
Is that okay?
还有别的医生
There are other doctors.
治疗不起作用
The treatment's not working.
昨晚她左肾衰竭 另一个也快了
Her left kidney failed last night. The other one's right behind it.
不是强直性脊椎炎
It's not ankylosing spondylitis.
肾活检显示 她得过IgA肾病
Kidney biopsy showed she had iga nephropathy,
可能是以下任一情况引起的
which could be caused by or associated with any of these conditions.
毫无头绪一下变千头万绪
We've gone from too few ideas to too many,
可病人时间不多了
and our patient's running out of time.
咋没看你容光焕发呢?
Why the lack of afterglow?
那妞没你想的么来劲?
Physio girl not as freaky as you'd hoped?
我和老婆回家了
I went home with my wife.
都到这份上了 你竟临阵退缩
After all that,you chickened out.
我不能这样伤害Rachel
I can't hurt Rachel like that.
镰状细胞性贫血能在血检中查出
Sickle cell anemia would have shown on blood tests.
无肠绒毛变平 排除腹腔问题
No flattened intestinal villi rules out celiac.
不是吧?
Seriously?
病人快死了 还揪着我性生活不放?
Our patient's dying,and we can't move past my sex life?
难不成拿你开涮15秒会耽误救人?
Seriously,you'd think it'd kill her if we spend 15 seconds mocking you?
时间到了
Time's up.
肝酶素正常 排除乙肝和肝硬化
Normal liver enzymes rules out hep b and cirrhosis.
奥尔波特综合症和 抗肾小球基底膜抗体都不可治愈
Alport and anti-gbm antibody are both untreatable,
她要得了咱就没辙了
so if she has them we can't help her.
也不是过敏性紫癜
And it can't be henoch-schonlein purpura.
没呼吸道感染和疹子
No inciting respiratory infection and no rash.
别用排除法了 说有可能的
I don't care what it's not. I want to know what it could be.
没排除的都有可能
Well,everything left on the list.
总有个先来后到吧
The list was not created equal.
人还分三六九等呢
Neither was man,by the way.
可能是血色沉着病
Hemochromatosis is a possibility.
铁过量沉积 引起全身的问题
Excess iron builds up,causes problems throughout the body.
威尔综合征也会影响多个系统
Weil's syndrome also affects multiple organ systems,
而且急诊给的抗生素不管用
and it wouldn't have been treated by the antibiotic the E. R. gave her.
结节病也说得通
Sarcoidosis makes sense too.
那好 按这三种病治
Good. Treat for those three.
我觉得你应该打给Tom
I think you should call Tom.
我快死了?
Am I gonna die?
不知道
I don't know.
如果他现在走进门
If he walked in here right now,
看见他 我脑子里只想到"骗子"
I'd look in his face and all I would think is "liar.
你不觉得这不公平吗?
" Don't you think that's kind of unfair?
你说最重要的是坦诚
You say honesty's all-important,
但你有没想过 有些事实会伤害人
but you conveniently ignore the truth that some truths hurt people.
Tom撒谎是为了保护你
Tom lied to protect you.
他是为自保
He was covering his ass.
我不是说钱的事
I'm not talking about the money.
Tom一年多没和别人上床了
Tom hasn't slept with anyone else in over a year.
他告诉你的?
He told you that?
这段婚姻只建立在假象上?
So my entire marriage is a sham?
不
No.
你丈夫只要你一个
Your husband,who only wants you,
骗你是为了你幸福
lied so that you could be happy.
在我看来 这种感情真实不过
That seems pretty real to me.
进来
Yeah?
听着 对不起
Listen,I'm sorry.
我也是 我不该这样说--
Me too. I shouldn't have said--
不 你没说错 我当时很自私
no,you were right. I was selfish back then.
我在试着改
I'm trying to change.
不知是因为House还是别的 但...
And I don't know if it's House or what,but...
你也变了
you're different too.
我也在试着改变
I'm trying.
我以为自己一直在促和谐保稳定
I always thought that I was keeping the peace,
其实我心里恨你 想逼你离开
but I was just resenting you and giving you a reason to leave.
我们要十年前吵这架就好了
I wish we had this fight ten years ago.
这功劳别记House头上行么?
Is it okay if we don't give House the credit?
我赞成
Oh,I recommend it.
三种都不是 肾脏仍在衰竭
"O" for three. Her kidney function is still declining.
得开始做透析了
We're gonna need to start dialysis.
老公回来了就好
Glad the husband's back.
小插曲错过几出 大结局不能不在
After missing so many little deaths,he should be here for the big one.
- 谁先来? - 结节性多动脉炎?
Top six,anyone? Polyarteritis nodosa?
那强的松应该起效
We'd have seen some improvement on prednisone.
老婆快死了 买花钱也可以省了
Guy's wife's dying,and he stops to buy flowers.
从他花园里采的 汞中毒符合
They're from his garden. Mercury poisoning fits.
紫丁香花
Those are lilacs.
我妈种过这花
My mom used to grow lilacs.
我爸让她铲了 因为太招蜜蜂
My dad made her get rid of them,'cause there were too many bees.
排除过敏性紫癜 因为没有呼吸道感染
We ruled out hsp 'cause there was no inciting respiratory infection.
但有些罕见病例 蜜蜂蛰了也会发病
But in rare cases,it can also be triggered by a bee sting.
我们排除它 还因为没起疹子
We also ruled it out because there's no rash.
也许是我们没发现
Maybe we just didn't see it.
最近被蜜蜂蛰没?
Have you been stung by a bee recently?
大概一个月前
Uh,about a month ago.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
我认为你老婆得了过敏性紫癜
I think your wife has henoch-schonlein purpura.
由系统性血管炎导致
Systemic vasculitis can cause
病变和炎症遍布全身
lesions and inflammations throughout the body.
相当难缠
It's pretty awful,
难怪取个德国佬的名儿
which explains why it was named after a German.
其实是俩德国佬
Actually two germans.
病变可反映在心脏
Lesions can pop up in the heart,
有时是肾脏 但最常见的是皮肤
sometimes in the kidneys,but always on the skin.
就是说 你肯定哪儿起了疹子
Means you'd have a rash somewhere.
- 我没起 - 你说了不算
- I don't. - Not that you know of.
我得检查你全身的窟窿
Okay,I'm gonna have to check your holes.
从嘴巴开始 要是没发现 我就得耍流氓了
I'll start with the mouth. If there's nothing there,then things might have to get kinky.
说"啊"
Say aah.
想耍还是没耍成
I was kinda hoping for kinky.
到底好还是不好?
Is that good or bad?
给她静脉注射高剂量的 免疫球蛋白和环磷酰胺
We'll treat her with high-dose ivig and cyclophosphamide.
就没事了
You should be fine.
我会好的
I'm gonna be okay.
我爱你
I love you.
真感人啊
That is adorable.
撇开你还想和其他人上床
Other than you still wanting to have sex with other dudes,
他继续败家不说
and him bankrupting your family,
你俩算大团圆了
I think you kids are pretty much home free.
还有...
And...
- 你俩和好了? - 没
- You two made up? - No.
稍后谢我也不晚
You can thank me later.
我全押
I'm all-in.
那好
All right.
我认输
Fold.
* 昨日与你相遇 *
* met you yesterday *
* 你只匆匆一瞥 *
* out in the place where *
* 对我并不在意 *
* here in the corner of your eye *
* 你手捧一颗真心*
* Now you hold a heart *
* 却不是我给的 *
* that was not mine to give *
* 你的存在 *
* for I cannot feel alive *
* 使我生不如死 *
* the way that you are *
要帮忙吗?
you need a hand?
* 和你一起时 *
* The way that I am *
谢谢
thanks.
* 我这个人 *
* When I'm with you *
* 我所有感觉 *
* the way that I feel *
抱歉取消了昨晚的约会
sorry about canceling the other night.
我也是
Me too.
* 和你一起时 *
* The way that I am *
* 我这个人 *
* with you *
* 我所有感觉 *
* the way that I feel *
* 我多想拥有你 *
* the way that you want me *
想去别的地方吗?
you wanna go somewhere?